Yes, nice to meet you.
はい、初めましてー
Bye bye.
バイバーイ
It's alcohol.
お酒だよ
I ordered a drink.
お酒頼んだもん
Oh, you can't drink?
あ、飲めないの?
Sorry, I just asked if you liked this kind of thing or what your name was.
ごめんね、なんか、勝手にこういうの好きかどうか名前のか頼ん
It happened.
じゃ った
It's just alcohol.
お酒だもんだって
It's alcohol.
お酒だよ
a,
あ、
Well, I don't usually drink it at all.
じゃあ 全然普段飲まないんだ
Don't you often drink with other members?
なんかよくメンバーとかとお酒飲みみたいにしないの?
That's right.
そうなんだ
It's quite famous.
結構有名なの
Hey, you're definitely famous.
ねえ、絶対有名だよね
I'm sure it will just be missing.
欠損するだけだよね、きっと
How long have you been active?
どれくらい活動してるの?
now?
今?
What year?
何年目?
Is that a long ritual?
それって長い執法なの?
Will you be a veteran?
ベテランに入るの?
Well, I'm 19 now.
え、今19代で
How old is the youngest child?
一番若い子って何歳なの?
as a member.
メンバーで
Ah, there it is.
あ、いるんだ
I drank it.
飲んだ
You drank it.
飲んだじゃん
One more breath.
あと一息
picture,
え、
Do you know something?
何 か分かってる?
this.
これ
This is tea.
これお茶だよ
Oh, it's tea.
え、お茶だよ
I drank it.
飲んだ
Do you feel it?
感じるの?
Like, like, like.
いいね、いいね、いいね
full.
いっぱい
Oh, amazing.
お、すげえ
Amazing.
すごーい
Like, like, like.
いいね、いいね、いいね
Amazing.
すごーい
Yes, it's a bit when you bite into it.
そう、かじったらちょっとね
Good.
よいしょ
Looks like it's going to be Arthu.
アルチューになりそうって
That's scary, just a little.
やばいよ、ちょっと
I'm lucky though.
ラッキーなんだけどさ
You were awake.
起き上がってたね
What should I do in the kitchen?
どうしよう、台所が
I thought what would I do if I had already lost my belly button.
もうヘソピーしてたらどうしようと思ったよ
Isn't this a bit of a joke?
ちょっとこれ遊んでるちくりじゃない?
Let's touch on it first.
先触っちゃおう
This is just a joke.
遊んでるちくりじゃん、これ
Don't act like this with a face like this.
こんな顔してやりまくってんじゃない
of?
の?
The skin feels really nice.
肌 触りめちゃくちゃいいな
I don't know about calf pants.
キャフトパンツなんて分かんない
I thought it was a skirt when it was a protein jacket.
タンパクトだとスカートかと思ったんです
Everything is smooth with this face.
全部ツルツルじゃん、この顔で
It was pretty good, I should have eaten it.
結構よかったよ、食べておいたら
Because you can't do it and it's you.
だって出来ないしお前でしょって
I guess it's not a good drink.
良いお酒じゃないってかね
It's bad, it's bad, it's bad.
やばい、やばい、やばい